Finding Aid for Women’s League (University of Michigan) records, 1890-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Photographs 1907-1949
  - Michigan League Presidents and Women's League 1907-1949, 2 folders (Box 40)
    (lacking 1908-1925, 1931-1932, 1933-1935)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 40)
  - Women's League Presidents 1890-1925 and Student Faculty Hour meeting, 1948-1949 (Outsize Photos-UBimum) (Box 40)
- Scrapbooks 1933-1991 (Outsize)
  The Scrapbooks exist in two subseries. The first compiles newspaper clippings about events in the Michigan League building or catered by its staff. The second subseries includes more general scrapbooks that compile brochures and various newspaper clippings, including articles about the Union-League Merger, editorials, and the building itself.
  - Events at the League or Catered by the League
    - 1980-1984 (volume 1) (Volume 1)
    - 1984-1991 (volume 2) (Volume 2)
  - General
    - 1933-1965 (volume 3) (Volume 3)
    - 1965-1978 (volume 4) (Volume 4)
- Architectural Drawings, undated 1984-1987 (Outsize)
  The Architectural Drawings (Outsize) encompass the years 1984-1987 and consist of two oversize folders primarily containing floor plans, renderings, and landscape sketches for the dining and courtyard sections of the League. The architectural firms represented include: Fry Associates Architects and Planners, Office of the University Landscape Architect, Interior Design Service, TMP Associates, Inc., and The Hysen Group: Food Service Consultants.
  - Fry Associates Architects and Planners, undated 1985, 2 folders (Folder 1)
    (floor plans and architectural renderings of the kitchen, buffet, servery, dining room, outside entrances, and conservatory in the League)
  - Landscape and architectural drawings, various firms, undated 1984, 1987, 2 folders (Folder 2)
    (included are landscape drawings for the courtyard and garden areas, dining area floor plans, and design concepts for the main lobby, Hussy and Vandenburg Rooms, and the ceiling restoration)